<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[theromanticbloke]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[theromanticbloke]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/theromanticbloke/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 01:18:23 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/theromanticbloke/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/1b3a097f-bdf2-48f8-a24d-2597a70fddad.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/theromanticbloke/a-few-months-back-i-was-telling-one-of-my-mates-about-a-fan/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3cae570a-216b-4c9e-8e6d-6cb38a395473</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 01:17:44 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>My wife and I enjoy a few weekend breaks each year, just as a chance to have a break from the kids and remember that we're still a couple! The Yarra Valley is one of our favourite destinations, with it's beautiful scenery, brilliant wine and plethora of great places to stay (& it's also a cruise 45 minute drive from our home).For our little getaway last October, we chose Balgownie Estate due to the recommendation of a friend and we certainly weren't disappointed. We booked a one bedroom spa suite that was a perfect option for a romantic night away. The location of the spa allows you to gaze out over the rolling valleys beyond Yarra Glen (although our ground floor apartment meant that you needed to keep an eye out for other guests that were occasionally strolling by!) A very cosy and comfortable lounge area, roomy balcony and well sized kitchenette made the accommodation a superb spot to base yourself for some Yarra Valley touring.A few other highlights at Balgownie were the cellar door; fantastic wines, friendly and knowledgable service (the Maiden Gully Shiraz was one of the best reds I've ever had the pleasure of tasting). Dinner at Rae's Restaurant was delicious, both of us loved our meals (lamb shank and the fish) and once again, service was top notch. I really can't recommend Balgownie Estate highly enough... hopefully we'll return again soon.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/theromanticbloke/my-wife-and-i-enjoy-a-few-weekend-breaks-each-year-just-as/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">f92896ec-e74b-48f3-8345-165081b34a9b</guid>
            <pubDate>Wed, 20 Apr 2016 01:12:33 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>